{"_id":{"$oid":"587749fc42f5030fe9e45df8"},"updatedAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:18:52.949Z"},"createdAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:18:52.949Z"},"question":"How are the services of an OSI layer called, which can be used from the next higher OSI loyer?","answers":[{"answer":"Instances","solution":false},{"answer":"Services","solution":true},{"answer":"Sessions","solution":false},{"answer":"Protocols","solution":false}],"category":"OSI Model","__v":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"58774a0142f5030fe9e45df9"},"updatedAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:18:57.041Z"},"createdAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:18:57.041Z"},"question":"Which OSI layer is located between the transport layer and the data link layer?","answers":[{"answer":"Network Layer","solution":true},{"answer":"Application Layer","solution":false},{"answer":"Session Layer","solution":false},{"answer":"Physical Layer","solution":false}],"category":"OSI Model","__v":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"58774a0342f5030fe9e45dfa"},"updatedAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:18:59.557Z"},"createdAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:18:59.557Z"},"question":"What is the only OSI layer that can send information directly to its counterpart?","answers":[{"answer":"1. OSI layer","solution":true},{"answer":"2. OSI layer","solution":false},{"answer":"3. OSI layer","solution":false},{"answer":"4. OSI layer","solution":false}],"category":"OSI Model","__v":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"58774a0642f5030fe9e45dfb"},"updatedAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:19:02.022Z"},"createdAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:19:02.022Z"},"question":"What happens in the 5th OSI layer?","answers":[{"answer":"Encryption and decryption of data packets as well as compression and character conversion","solution":false},{"answer":"Control of logical connections in the network","solution":true},{"answer":"This is the top software level. The interface between user and computer","solution":false},{"answer":"The physical data transfer","solution":false}],"category":"OSI Model","__v":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"58774a0842f5030fe9e45dfc"},"updatedAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:19:04.346Z"},"createdAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:19:04.346Z"},"question":"In which OSI layer are routers to be classified?","answers":[{"answer":"Data Link Layer","solution":false},{"answer":"Network Layer","solution":true},{"answer":"Session Layer","solution":false},{"answer":"Application Layer","solution":false}],"category":"OSI Model","__v":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"58774a0a42f5030fe9e45dfd"},"updatedAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:19:06.389Z"},"createdAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:19:06.389Z"},"question":"What is the name of the 5th OSI layer?","answers":[{"answer":"Application Layer","solution":false},{"answer":"Transport Layer","solution":false},{"answer":"Session Layer","solution":true},{"answer":"Data Link Layer","solution":false}],"category":"OSI Model","__v":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"58774a0c42f5030fe9e45dfe"},"updatedAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:19:08.577Z"},"createdAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:19:08.577Z"},"question":"What is the OSI layer used for compression and encryption?","answers":[{"answer":"4. OSI layer","solution":false},{"answer":"5. OSI layer","solution":false},{"answer":"6. OSI layer","solution":true},{"answer":"7. OSI layer","solution":false}],"category":"OSI Model","__v":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"58774a0e42f5030fe9e45dff"},"updatedAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:19:10.623Z"},"createdAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:19:10.623Z"},"question":"In which OSI layer are cables and connectors to be classified?","answers":[{"answer":"1. OSI layer","solution":true},{"answer":"2. OSI layer","solution":false},{"answer":"3. OSI layer","solution":false},{"answer":"4. OSI layer","solution":false}],"category":"OSI Model","__v":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"58774a1042f5030fe9e45e00"},"updatedAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:19:12.851Z"},"createdAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:19:12.851Z"},"question":"What is the name of the 3rd OSI layer?","answers":[{"answer":"Application Layer","solution":false},{"answer":"Transport Layer","solution":false},{"answer":"Network Layer","solution":true},{"answer":"Session Layer","solution":false}],"category":"OSI Model","__v":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"58774a1242f5030fe9e45e01"},"updatedAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:19:14.737Z"},"createdAt":{"$date":"2017-01-12T09:19:14.737Z"},"question":"The TCP protocol is assigned to which OSI layer?","answers":[{"answer":"Transport Layer","solution":true},{"answer":"Session Layer","solution":false},{"answer":"Network Layer","solution":false},{"answer":"Presentation Layer","solution":false}],"category":"OSI Model","__v":0}
